<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>practical guide on RedBlackTech</title><link>https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/tags/practical-guide/</link><description>Recent content in practical guide on RedBlackTech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:35:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/tags/practical-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frameworks</title><link>https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/posts/framework/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:35:30 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/posts/framework/</guid><description>What exactly is a [Software] Framework? In our quest to take down popular tech buzzwords, we&amp;rsquo;re going to tackle Software Frameworks.
Definition A program that allows you to hook into itself to extend it.
That&amp;rsquo;s the one liner, but lets take it apart through an example that is your operating system.
A running operating system is a process that provides a framework for running other processes. Each process can spawn child processes, which leads to a tree/heirarchy of processes that we can view through a command like htop.</description></item><item><title>What is DevOps?</title><link>https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/posts/devops/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 19:45:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://red-black-tech.github.io/staging/posts/devops/</guid><description>Definition The subdomain of Software Engineering focused on deploying software quickly.
Simple as that.
Strangely, even though DevOps is a major buzzword in tech, many online struggle to provide a useful definition for DevOps. Take a look at Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s definition:
&amp;ldquo;DevOps is the union of people, process, and technology to continually provide value to customers&amp;rdquo;
That is not a precise enough definition to be useful. There are so many things that definition applies to, a lot of them totally unrelated to tech (think about it: Even a financial consulting company would fall under such a definition).</description></item></channel></rss>